themehunt.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy - ThemeHunt

Corlate is available for WordPress with Free Page Builder! [Download Free](https://themehunt.com/item/1527563-corlate-free-business-agency-wordpress-theme-with-page-builder)

Total Items: 331 Community Users: 378923

### Introduction

ThemeHunt values the privacy and security of the information seriously that you share with us through ThemeHunt. It is important that you understand how we collect, use, and maintain your information. This Privacy Policy deals with personally identifiable information (referred to as "Data" below) that may be collected by us on our site.

By submitting personally identifiable information on themehunt.com, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy and you explicitly consent to the collection, use of your personally identifiable information in accordance with this privacy policy.

This Privacy Policy (last updated on May 24, 2018) does not apply to other entities that we do not own or control or persons that are not our employees, agents or within our control. Please take time to read our [Terms & Conditions.](https://themehunt.com/terms-conditions)

### What types of data we collect

 **Personal Information:** The personal information includes your name, address information, email address and URL, telephone number, account username and password, credit/debit card numbers and associated billing addresses (if intended to make a purchase of any service from us) and expiration dates, account numbers, as well as other, similar information. Such information is only collected from you if you voluntarily submit it to us.

**Non-Personal Information:** The Non-Personal Data includes information that cannot be used to identify or contact you, like demographic information regarding, for example, user IP addresses, browser types and other anonymous statistical information that includes the use of ThemeHunt website.

### Who has the access to your data

We do not share your personal data with any third-party in a way that reveals your personal information like email, name, etcetera (subject to laws and regulations). Only ThemeHunt  site administrators have access to these data. However, you can review, update and delete your data whenever you want.

### What purposes your data are used for

These data help us identify you as our customer/subscriber/patron and deliver products/notices and other marketing materials. As you can not purchase any product or subscribe to newsletter or leave comments anonymously. So, this is the only means we can identify you as our customer/subscriber/patron and allow you to make these actions on the site.

### How long ThemeHunt retains your information

When you register for a ThemeHunt account, we process and keep your personal data we have about you for as long as you don’t delete the account/unsubscribe yourself (subject to laws and regulations).

### What we don’t do with your personal data

We do not and will never share, disclose, sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personal data to other companies for the marketing of their own products or services.

### How we process these data 

We use your personally identifiable data (name, email address, etc.) to identify you to contact, send newsletter, and provide products & supports. The non-personal data may be used to improve the service.

### What rights you have over your data 

If you have an account on ThemeHunt site, or leave comments, you can request a copy of your information we have about you. You can also request us to delete your data from our site. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for security, legal or administrative purposes.

### Third party links on our site 

We may talk about third party products and services on our website. These third party sites have their own privacy policies. So, therefore, we have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.

### What policy we have for children

We recognize we have a special obligation to protect personal data obtained from children. We do not and will not knowingly collect personal data from any child under 16 without consent from their parent or guardian. If you are a parent or guardian and are concerned about the transfer of personal data about your child, please contact with us.

### What our cookies do on your browser

ThemeHunt site uses cookies to identify and track visitors, their actions on the site, and their website access preferences. The visitors on themehunt.com who do not wish to have cookies placed on their browsers should turn off cookies before using ThemeHunt. Once you turn off cookies on your browsers, some features of themehunt.com may not work properly without the aid of cookies.

### What data breach procedures we have in place

If in any case a breach of data such as loss, alteration, unauthorised disclosure or access, personal data transmission, storage or otherwise processed happens, we will notify you immediately after we become aware of.

### How you can review, update, get a copy or delete your data

You can review and update your data on our site at any time by going to your account details. If you want to delete or get a copy of your personal data, send a mail to [[email protected]](https://themehunt.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) . We will do that with immediate effect.

### What if we make changes to our Privacy Policy 

Any change made or any new point added to the Privacy Policy described above will be published here on this page. The major changes will also be informed through newsletter.

### Join Our Newsletter

Want more Bootstrap themes & templates? Subscribe to our mailing list to receive an update when new items arrive!
